[{"answer": "It was the same person that was on top whether they were T- shaped to the sidewalk.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "The person on the top was back against where?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "Absolutely and ironically, Piers, the witnesses were supposed to be on the stand for the state, but it appears the testimony they gave very much benefits the defense.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Martin, what a dramatic day today and if to date we felt that perhaps the state was beginning to win the argument, today very much a better day you would say for the defense?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "Well, going back to when they were vertical, I could tell the person on the bottom had a lighter skin color, correct.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "In terms of describing the individuals, are you able to describe their faces or anything, or just clothing descriptions?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What you saw was the person on top in an MMA-style straddle position, correct?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "That was further described, was it not, as being ground and pound?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, that is certainly the way the prosecution wanted to end the day and they were able to do that by talking to a physician's assistant, George Zimmerman's physician's assistant, who said on his medical records that he had listed, he had been keeping fit by doing training.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "That it's more likely to have been the guy that's been training in that very form of martial arts?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "So the basic point is if everybody is contradicting each other and even themselves in various testimony that they've given in depositions, is that enough for reasonable doubt?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I think he was a strong witness and a good witness for the defense, even though he was put on as a prosecution witness.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Put it all together, what are you thinking?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "I don't think you can tell at this point.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Before you leave me, one word, is he going to be found guilty or not, George Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Was that the context in which that happened?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "No, I really wouldn't.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "I can't -- I can't confirm that or deny that at this time, but I think what is important here is they have put forth that and I think Mr. Good's testimony is real important.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Do you know if Trayvon Martin ever trained for MMA style martial arts himself?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Piers, I'd have to respectfully disagree.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Is there a racial element to this that you're now concerned about, in the sense that were they just not engaged with a young black girl giving evidence in the same way that they were engaged, apparently, with a eloquent, middle-class white man?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "I sometimes talked to her, but not -- nothing serious.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Did you speak to her at all?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "I was shocked.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "When she gave evidence, what was your reaction to the criticism and support she received?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we go to Norland that's how we talk.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "When she talked about, you know, creepy ass crackers and that kind of thing, did you think she was using terms that are racist or just terms that young people use these days in the era that she comes from?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "I'm not racist because I'm from England but that's just how people in Florida describe white people, that's what I know.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Is it in terms of your experience, is it a racist term against white people?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "AKANLU: No, he -- I just know he went to my middle school, but I never seen him before.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Did you know Trayvon Martin at all?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Some of it I do not.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Are you unable to read that at all?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I don't understand cursive.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Can you read any of the words on it?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Were you surprised she couldn't read her own letter?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "It's sad.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "In terms of the reaction that Rachel has had, a lot of very nasty criticism has come her way as somebody that knew her, not that well but you knew her, what do you feel about that, that this young woman has been put through so much real attack from many quarters?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, certainly that's going to be the bottom line in their reviewing each one on these witnesses that comes forth is that they're going to rely upon their own life experiences, and I think what was interesting about Rachel is that for many of these people, the jurors, they may have needed a cultural anthropologist to explain some of her responses but that's not going to happen.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Is that how you're seeing this?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "I certainly agree that the defense had a great day today.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I have a question for the legal analysts on the panel and that is, there's obviously focus on what happened during the -- during the fight.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Yes, Jo-Ellan?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "That's a great point.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Judge Alex?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "You described him as a creepy ass cracker?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "So it was racial, but it was because Trayvon Martin put race in this?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "You don't think that's a racial comment?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I think -- well let me talk about the representation of Rachel Jeantel because I think that's important and a lot of that is wrapped up in a lot of the racism, classism, sexism and just a lot of the lookism that's deeply rooted in this country.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Sherri, is it about race, this trial?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "But is it impossible to eliminate race from this?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Well, I do think that it would have an impact on the jury, how she comes across on the witness stand, and it may be that some people who are on the jury are not understanding some of the issues of race and class that -- that have been brought up by the guests and -- but I might add that, you know, we do have this image of Oprah Winfrey who has been at some point large and African American and female and she's been one of the most loved persons in our country if not the world.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "When you see the reaction, putting that to one side, what kind of impact would it have on the legality of the court process itself do you think?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Yes, I think you're absolutely right.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "What is your take on it all?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "You could, and I will never say it won't happen, but I would be very surprised, and in constantly talking with those, it's unlikely he'd take the stand.", "docId": "130628pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Could we at any moment be sprung that as a huge surprise?", "qSentId": 454}]